♪ They tried to make me go to rehab ♪
♪ I said no, no, no ♪
(lively upbeat music)
♪ Yes, I've been black,
but when I come back ♪
♪ You'll know, know, know ♪
♪ I ain't got the time and
if my daddy thinks I'm fine ♪
♪ Just try to make me go to rehab ♪
♪ I won't go, go, go ♪
♪ I'd rather be at home with Ray ♪
♪ I ain't got seventy days ♪
♪ 'Cause there's nothing ♪
♪ There's nothing you can teach me ♪
♪ That I can't learn from Mr. Hathaway ♪
♪ I didn't get a lot in class ♪
♪ But I know it don't
come in a shot glass ♪
♪ They tried to make me go
to rehab, I said no, no, no ♪
♪ Yes, I've been black,
but when I come back ♪
♪ You'll know, know, know ♪
♪ I ain't got the time and
if my daddy thinks I'm fine ♪
♪ Just try to make me go to
rehab, I won't go, go, go ♪
♪ The man said, "Why do
you think you're here" ♪
♪ I said, "I got no idea" ♪
♪ I'm gonna, I'm gonna lose my baby ♪
♪ So I always keep a bottle near ♪
♪ He said, "I just think
you're depressed" ♪
♪ This me, "Yeah, baby, and the rest" ♪
♪ They tried to make me go to
rehab but I said no, no, no ♪
♪ Yes, I've been black,
but when I come back ♪
♪ You'll know, know, know ♪
♪ I don't ever wanna drink again ♪
♪ I just, ooh, I just need a friend ♪
♪ I'm not gonna spend ten weeks ♪
♪ Have everyone think I'm on the mend ♪
♪ It's not just my pride ♪
♪ It's just 'til these tears have dried ♪
♪ They tried to make me go to
rehab, but I said no, no, no ♪
♪ Yes, I've been black,
but when I come back ♪
♪ You'll know, know, know ♪
♪ I ain't got the time and
if my daddy thinks I'm fine ♪
♪ Just try to make me go to rehab ♪
♪ I won't go, go, go ♪
(lively upbeat music swells)